Xiaojing
it is good
In the near future
Territorial disputes in East Asian waters continue to intensify
Kaledoruf, an island country located in East Asian waters
Unite with neighboring countries that hate the interference of great powers
Established a national community named after the East Asian Federation
East Asian Federation incites radical nationalism
Advocating the restoration of territories and the development of maritime forces
The crisis of military conflicts off the coast of Japan is also approaching
Approximately 450 kilometers west of Okinotori Island off the coast of the Haruma Islands
December 23, 03:15 JST (Japan Standard Time)
Patrol Ship Black Island
The air pressure is dropping sharply
The heavy rainfall area is approaching the ship
21 degrees 23 minutes north latitude 132 degrees 14 minutes east longitude
There are 20 ships, so many
I don’t look like a serious fishing boat, it’s bound for Chudao
Captain, if those ships move on
May cross the water boundary into the territorial waters
Request support from the headquarters
Yes
Get down
mushroom
poster
TTG
Film source
kokoben
translation
There were 20 fishing boats of unknown nationality early this morning
Rain andSasa
From the exclusive economic zone of the Hatsushima waters of the Teruma Islands to the territorial sea boundary
The patrol ship in the Hauruma Special Control Area of ​​the Coast Guard
Go to the scene urgently
The fishing boat suddenly opened fire at 3:24 in the morning
Touch the pear duck
translation
Communication was interrupted after Black Island reported that several people were injured
The crew of the fishing boat boarded Hatsushima
The maritime security officers may have been detained
There is also news that a flag like a national flag has been raised in the middle of the island
Fairy water
Proofreading and post
what
Does it mean that Hatsushima is occupied?
Armed forces disguised as fishermen
Isn't it the East Asian Federation?
Many neighboring countries have claimed ownership of the Boriu Islands
shilly
time
Among them, the one who claims the strongest and repeatedly violated territorial water
East Asian Federation
3 years ago they unilaterally announced the founding of the nation
There is no international common sense
The United States, China and Russia contain each other
time
Acha and painted face
The UN can't intervene
If they really came to take Hatsushima
I have issued an order for maritime security operations
Prime Minister, in this situation, you should order the defense to be deployed.
Malala
time
Intelligence is not enough
First determine the identity and purpose of the illegal lander
Minister of Foreign Affairs, please check with relevant countries
And file a complaint with the United Nations
understood
Maritime Self-Defense Force
Has been urgently dispatched to conduct exercises in the southwestern waters of the Ogasawara Islands
The 5th Guard Group headed to Hatsushima
5th Guard Group
Is Iphone?
Frigate Aihawk
Combat Information Center This is the bridge, there is no target in sight
Received, keep course and speed
Frigate Isokaze
No abnormalities in the deck
Frigate first snow
Conduct a comprehensive inspection of the main gun
Roger that
Frigate Shirayuki
Good view, now in 20 kilometers sea area
Submarine morning tide
Steering without echo
Aircraft-mounted frigate Ibuki
Aircraft Carrier Ibuki
Anyone can tell that this is an attacking aircraft carrier, right?
Main specifications of the aircraft-mounted frigate DDV192 Ibuki
right
Owning this is obviously against the constitution in our country
What do you say
No, Ibuki is just for defensive purposes
Is a means of self-defense
against war
No aircraft carrier
This is against the constitution
For our country with 6,800 islands
Ibuki Service Strong Guild
Configure Ibuki to ensure air superiority
By no means to break away from the purpose of defensive defense
I am sure that I will not disappoint the people's expectations
Against war offensive
Captain, the commander is looking for you
Please go back to the battle information center
understood
Captain Ibuki Ryota Akizu 1 Sa