Xiaojing
it is good
In the near future
Territorial disputes in East Asian waters continue to intensify
Kaledoruf, an island country located in East Asian waters
Unite with neighboring countries that hate the interference of great powers
Established a national community named after the East Asian Federation
East Asian Federation incites radical nationalism
Advocating the restoration of territories and the development of maritime forces
The crisis of military conflicts off the coast of Japan is also approaching
Approximately 450 kilometers west of Okinotori Island off the coast of the Haruma Islands
December 23, 03:15 JST (Japan Standard Time)
Patrol Ship Black Island
The air pressure is dropping sharply
The heavy rainfall area is approaching the ship
21 degrees 23 minutes north latitude 132 degrees 14 minutes east longitude
There are 20 ships, so many
I don’t look like a serious fishing boat, it’s bound for Chudao
Captain, if those ships move on
May cross the water boundary into the territorial waters
Request support from the headquarters
Yes
Get down
mushroom
poster
TTG
Film source
kokoben
translation
There were 20 fishing boats of unknown nationality early this morning
Rain andSasa
From the exclusive economic zone of the Hatsushima waters of the Teruma Islands to the territorial sea boundary
The patrol ship in the Hauruma Special Control Area of ​​the Coast Guard
Go to the scene urgently
The fishing boat suddenly opened fire at 3:24 in the morning
Touch the pear duck
translation
Communication was interrupted after Black Island reported that several people were injured
The crew of the fishing boat boarded Hatsushima
The maritime security officers may have been detained
There is also news that a flag like a national flag has been raised in the middle of the island
Fairy water
Proofreading and post
what
Does it mean that Hatsushima is occupied?
Armed forces disguised as fishermen
Isn't it the East Asian Federation?
Many neighboring countries have claimed ownership of the Boriu Islands
shilly
time
Among them, the one who claims the strongest and repeatedly violated territorial water
East Asian Federation
3 years ago they unilaterally announced the founding of the nation
There is no international common sense
The United States, China and Russia contain each other
time
Acha and painted face
The UN can't intervene
If they really came to take Hatsushima
I have issued an order for maritime security operations
Prime Minister, in this situation, you should order the defense to be deployed.
Malala
time
Intelligence is not enough
First determine the identity and purpose of the illegal lander
Minister of Foreign Affairs, please check with relevant countries
And file a complaint with the United Nations
understood
Maritime Self-Defense Force
Has been urgently dispatched to conduct exercises in the southwestern waters of the Ogasawara Islands
The 5th Guard Group headed to Hatsushima
5th Guard Group
Is Iphone?
Frigate Aihawk
Combat Information Center This is the bridge, there is no target in sight
Received, keep course and speed
Frigate Isokaze
No abnormalities in the deck
Frigate first snow
Conduct a comprehensive inspection of the main gun
Roger that
Frigate Shirayuki
Good view, now in 20 kilometers sea area
Submarine morning tide
Steering without echo
Aircraft-mounted frigate Ibuki
Aircraft Carrier Ibuki
Anyone can tell that this is an attacking aircraft carrier, right?
Main specifications of the aircraft-mounted frigate DDV192 Ibuki
right
Owning this is obviously against the constitution in our country
What do you say
No, Ibuki is just for defensive purposes
Is a means of self-defense
against war
No aircraft carrier
This is against the constitution
For our country with 6,800 islands
Ibuki Service Strong Guild
Configure Ibuki to ensure air superiority
By no means to break away from the purpose of defensive defense
I am sure that I will not disappoint the people's expectations
Against war offensive
Captain, the commander is looking for you
Please go back to the battle information center
understood
Captain Ibuki Ryota Akizu 1 Sa
Sure enough, did the above ask for maritime security operations?
I don't know where the other party is yet
Xinbo, it's difficult to deploy defense
If it is the East Asian Federation
The number of weapons and personnel flowing through the peninsula should not be underestimated
It used to be the station of the US military
So familiar with the operation of the army
If they have calculated that we will be dispatched
Must have been calculated
If you want to kill Japan
Then they must really want Ibuki’s combat power data
They will take the initiative to attack us
Ensuring the aviation advantage of the sea area is the most important
Having said that, at this time we have visitors on board
Captain Akitsu was originally the ace pilot of the Air Self-Defense Force, right?
I did fly a fighter jet
So why did you become the captain of the aircraft carrier again?
Should imitate the tradition of the US military
The fighter pilot serves as the captain of the aircraft carrier
But for the conflicting viewpoints that aircraft carriers are strategic weapons and specialized defenses
What do you think?
Does Japan need Ibuki
This is not a question I should answer
Please let me hear your thoughts as a captain
Not a question I should answer
So early
Good morning
early
Just do it before breakfast
The gap between us and online media is really getting bigger
Your Toho Shimbun is so famous, why is it humble?
Is this the interview yesterday
Yes, there is no gain at all
After all, this ship was controversial before it sailed.
So I want us to interview to gain people’s understanding
However, the captain didn’t mean to cooperate at all
But the deputy captain is very kind
Those two were classmates from the Defense University, they were vying for the first place.
Then on to Ibuki, Mr. Shinba of the Maritime Self-Defense Force is the deputy captain.
Mr. Qiuzu of the Air Self-Defense Force became the captain
So there should be some reason, right
That's it
All relevant countries have denied any connection with this matter
Because there is no formal diplomatic window with the East Asian Federation
We are currently in contact with them through a third country
Prime Minister Our country is under invasion
Shouldn't we take strong and resolute measures?
It feels very inconvenient to wear this action
You can't play golf here, right?
That's true
Safety must be considered
Yes
Please wear this when you leave the room
okay, I get it
By the way, the maritime security operation was carried out because something happened?
I'll explain this to you later
Actually let us run into a security operation in Shanghai
Nothing is luckier than this
Since the establishment of the Self-Defense Forces, this order has only been issued three times.
Mr. Yokoyama, right
You deserve to be a reporter from University of Tanaka
I really know the Self-Defense Forces
Isn't that said?
Only 2 of us out of 100 media
Such good luck is still going on
Stop the interview or something, please forgive me
I'm sorry because this is no longer a sailing exercise
Please try not to leave this non-commissioned officer preparation room
Flipper No. 1 calls the Ibuki Battle Information Center
A fishing boat sends out a rescue signal on the course
Flipper
Which country’s ship sent the rescue signal
Unable to confirm
Is it related to the first island landing?
Commander, please give an anti-submarine alert order
not
Combat Information Center
Missile launch sound is detected, it’s a submarine
15 nautical miles ahead of the fleet at 10 o'clock
Did you call me suddenly?
Was ambushed
There are 12 missiles
Aihawk interceptor missile
That's too late
The artillery commander fires jamming bombs to respond to the near defense system
Air combat begins, intercepting near defense system, launching jamming bomb
The target distance of 2500 is about to enter the range of the close defense system
shooting
A missile strikes
Everyone prevents shocks
what
Release water release water
Put out the fire. Deck equipment caught fire. Ask for support
Prevent the fire from spreading and bypass it
No way, please support
Was hit by a missile and exploded
This is the Chief of Emergency
Shot behind the deck and broke a hole
Damaged aircraft lifts and electrical systems
Neither lift can move
How long does it take to repair
24 hours not fast, 20 hours
Please fix it within 12 hours
Can't the carrier-based aircraft be dispatched until it is repaired?
Please, it's okay, cheer up
A Island A Island
Go to the cafeteria, don't panic
Chief Medical Officer Chief Medical Officer
Are you injured?
No
what happened
It's okay. It's safe in the room
Please go in please go in
Please, please, go in, please go in
Isn't this being attacked?
The submarine that attacked Ibuki escaped from the sea area at the scene
The fishing boat also disappeared
Prime Minister, this is the level of defense deployment, right?
The new mobile unit is approaching the waters of the Boriu Islands
Mobile force
The Northern Fleet of the East Asian Federation is based on the aircraft carrier Gilxia
It really is the East Asian Federation
The prime minister, let's give the defense dispatch order.
Prime Minister
They sent an aircraft carrier
The appearance looks like an old antique from a former communist country
The internal structure is upgraded
There are several carrier-based aircraft
MiG-35 60
The air-to-sea alert level is raised to strict
This is tricky
commander
Use a helicopter to transfer the reporters to the supply ship heading south.
Ok this is better
Ship sentinel, third deployment, first sentinel
satellite telephone?
I can’t use my phone at sea, so I told me to take it
But you can’t send messages without permission
Yes
Good morning
Miss Shaigu
Someone posted this video on the Internet not long ago
what
You are also very beautiful today
Thank you
Seems something is burning
Asked the Coast Guard
No news of fires and accidents in large ships
Know the location
Have location information
About 400 kilometers west of the Ogasawara Islands
Zoom in
Yes
Huh, do you want to interview again?
Mr. Fujitang, you really like boats
Is it Ichu?
Haven't we been in the Maritime Self-Defense Force special episode?
Look at DDV192 Ichu
DDV192 Ibuki
Aircraft-mounted frigate
The first aircraft-mounted frigate after the war
The largest vessel of the Maritime Self-Defense Force 248m
No way
Damn
Ah, she's on this ship right now
Just above
On top, Yuko
interviewing
Vice President Bates
Regarding this unfair aggression against us
We intend to retake the territory immediately
I will convey it to the president who is attending the US-China-Russia trilateral meeting
But I hope you can restrain yourself
of course
But we may have to use your country’s power as an ally
I will convey it to Mr. President good luck
Sonar buoy contact found submarine
20 miles ahead of the fleet, 320 depth
No response to identification signal
The commander is a submarine of the East Asian Federation
On the heading to Boriu
If we go straight, will there be a fight?
Yes
In this case, our challenge is inevitable
Should be avoided
Do not
Should go straight
This battle is also a battle against time
If the enemy completes the defensive deployment
Whether you want to recapture Hatsushima or rescue the maritime security officer
Will become more difficult
But in that case
To succumb to threats or to fight
The test is our consciousness
Have you finished your two opinions?
Yes
it is good
straight
All members enter combat positions Repeat All members enter combat positions
What are you fighting with?
Faster
Yes
Emergency closing of the cabin door
Drive to the front of Ibuki at maximum speed
Maximum speed
The artillery commander prepares to fight against the submarine
Preparation for launch of submarine missile
Ready to launch
The sound of the torpedo tube opening
Are you going to do it here?
The morning tide also opened the torpedo tube
Captain Qiujin, what's your judgment?
The enemy's finger is already pulling the trigger
We can avoid torpedoes in the sea
But it’s dangerous to face the morning tide at close range
If we do not act, we will be attacked
I think the current situation meets the conditions of the attack
Our mission is maritime security operations
Except for legitimate defense, we cannot attack actively
Obviously the current state of affairs is that we have been improperly violated
Once you do it, it's war
This is the obstacle we have to overcome
2 miles away
2 minutes to reach the goal
Commander, please give an attack order
If you sink an enemy submarine
Not only will it affect the safety of Hatsushima’s marine protection team
Will also create new excuses for the enemy to attack
Do you want the morning tide ship as a living sacrifice?
I didn't say that
Trust the control skills of Captain Taki and his crew
Alright
We are not allowed to fire a bullet before the enemy fires
Keep attacking and keep going
Maintain course and speed
Commander commander
Send the commander to the infirmary
stretcher
commander
Stretcher, hurry up
Commander, are you okay?
1 minute to reach directly above the target
15 seconds
10 seconds
Pass directly above the enemy submarine
Didn't you call?
The fleet broke through the predicted line of attack
Ah great
The enemy submarine’s course turned northeast and disengaged
If everything is calm in the future
The Ibuki will reach the waters of Kurume at 24:00 as planned
They do well
The nature of our country’s defense is not to evade. They showed this
You are consequential
If the enemy opens fire, I am afraid now
Prime Minister
We should immediately order the defense to attack
However, Commander Wakui was seriously injured and unable to continue his command.
Who will be the commander from now on
Command will be transferred to Ibuki Captain Akizu Kazusa
Akitsu
This is Captain Akizu Kazusa
I'm Qiujin, who is instructed to take over
It is said that you are the youngest person to be promoted to Izuo
It’s very hard to transfer from the Air Self-Defense Force to the Maritime Self-Defense Force.
Are you still used to it?
Once people get new toys, they will be eager to try
It depends on whether the people who master it have firm mental preparation
The warship that invested 300 billion in heavy taxes is a toy in his mouth
Your idea is correct
I hurt my ears, it feels like the sky is spinning, so troublesome
Akitsu Kazusa
I hand over the command of the Fifth Guard Group to you
Yes
As you wish
Next time they will attack
We must overcome this obstacle anyway
What obstacle
For those who try to violate our sovereignty
Be prepared to face off
So I don't escape
Let the other party see our will to defend the country
Will definitely die
Since its establishment, it is the pride of our Self-Defense Force that no one died
wrong
What we are proud of is not that the Self-Defense Force did not have any dead
It’s that in the decades after the war, no one died because of the war.
If you die to protect the people
Isn't this the long-cherished wish of the self-defense officer?
Intervention in the tripartite containment of the United States, China and Russia
See if we can get results that are beneficial to us
Sawasaki
Is the opponent’s purpose only to occupy Poliujian and make it a fait accompli?
Restoration of the territory of the Kaledoruf Dynasty
It is a convention that supports the military regime of the East Asian Federation
But things will not be so simple
Good or bad
The world's dominant country has lost its original status
Let national firstism spread all over the world
Caused the rise of nationalist countries like the East Asian Federation
But the armaments expanded so fast
They can't do it on their own
In other words, is there a country that is behind it?
If you manipulate it behind your back, you can make the other party invisible
Indeed, our country’s national strength and combat power are stronger than the East Asian Federation
But if we enter a total war
Both sides will be fatally injured
Sawazaki Yusaku
Director, Asian and Oceanian Bureau, Ministry of Foreign Affairs
On the territorial issue
If Japan cannot maintain the status quo
May be unavoidable
But if not handled properly
The war will spread to Asia, not the whole world
The next 24 hours is the key
Yes
Thank you slow walk
Thank you
Shop manager, let me do it
Great
Look, the boots for Christmas candy are sold out
Replenishment is hard to come
I must step up now
I will concentrate on this
Yes
That Xiaojing
Can i ask you for tomorrow night shift
what
Oops, Yasuo got the flu
Can't it? It's Christmas Eve after all
Isn't that okay? After all, tomorrow is Christmas Eve
I have no problem
Yeah, I knew you would agree
Thank you, I went to make boots
I'll leave it to you outside
Hotan, Hotan, please
Yes Yes
Oh, go here a little bit more, put your heart in order
-Yes-Please
Captain, Hatsushima is ahead
Radar contact 1-9-0
16 Angle 10 is approaching
Only at this distance did it detect that it should be a stealth machine
If it’s the East Asian Federation, it’s the MiG-35.
Visually confirm the target
Warning It is forbidden to fly over Hatsushima
Please evacuate from this airspace immediately
Do not make jokes
Is it you who invaded the air?
Naha Command Center, this is Doug 2
I got a warning shot
Doug 2 This is the Naha Command Center
Please make a U-turn and return, repeat, please return to base immediately
Receive and return immediately
But to complete your mission to shoot Hatsushima
understand
Radar wave detected
We are locked and call here
It's a missile, turn right and maneuver to evade!
Doug 2 Please answer this is the Naha Command Center
Repeat Doug 2 Please answer this is the Naha Command Center
Doug 2 please answer
The dead?
Is the message sure?
A reconnaissance plane of the Air Self-Defense Force was shot down
Unable to confirm whether the pilot escaped
I'm afraid the chance of survival is slim
Prime Minister should have fully satisfied the conditions now
If you don’t make up your mind, this battle will be lost.
Prime Minister
Japanese territory is being invaded
It is already certain that we were attacked by force
After the Minister of Defense obtained the consent of all cabinet members
Seek the consent of Congress afterwards
Now order all the troops of the Self-Defense Force to be deployed
Yes
Minister of Foreign Affairs, now contact the UN quickly
To report that our country will exercise its right of self-defense
understood
Captain Ibuki gave orders to each ship
The defense is dispatched!
This is not a drill
repeat
Defence dispatched
Raise the level of air and submarine alert to strict
Order the defense to be dispatched!
What is the defense?
This is incredible
-This is a fighting condition-Is this the first time
Yes, this is the first time we ordered the use of force after World War II
Is there going to be a war? Isn't this ship dangerous?
It's okay, it's okay, the boat is so big
Generally speaking, war and battle are not the same
-What's the difference? -Eh
Japan has always believed that peace can be maintained even without the use of force
Am I going to be the first prime minister to discover that this is just a fantasy
Shi Du, how can I bear this responsibility?
I will guard the peace and independence of our country
Take on the mission of the Self-Defense Force
Compliance with the Japanese Constitution and laws
Unity and strict discipline
Chongde Shangzhi Respect for personality
Strengthen fitness, improve skills
Not participating in political activities
Concentrate on performing duties with a strong sense of responsibility
-Don't be afraid of danger-Don't be afraid of danger
Dedicate yourself to your mission
Live up to the national trust
I swear
The pilot who fell from the sky above Boriu
At the moment of being hit by a missile
Must be reciting this vow silently
I must avenge the two of them
Yuanshang
If you go to the battlefield with this kind of thought, you will be blinded
Yes
We are not going to avenge the enemy
If we must use strength to make them understand
Their military operations to invade our Asian territorial waters
If you are so arrogant, reckless and stupid, tell them with your strength
The defense was deployed to prove our strength
The deck is 248 meters long
There are 720 members serving on this ship
In this fighter
With 60 barrels of fuel
Haven't seen the smoke yet
Yes
I can't get in touch anymore
Is it shut down?
Ok
-Fujitang-Yes
-Please sort out Ibuki's information.-Okay
Just use the existing materials to make another special
-I see.-The interest of users has been hooked.
It is our job to make them interested
"Japan's first aircraft carrier Ibuki"
"The secret operation in the Pacific Ocean now reveals its full story"
You know what i want
Isn't it long?
not long
Holler
The shop manager has already booked all the chicken for Christmas
-Manager.-I was scared to death
Scared me
Sorry sorry
I brought earplugs for concentration
what happened? Ah scared me
That one
The chicken for Christmas has all been reserved
How much do I need to order more
30...ah, not 50 copies.
Ok
This is really a sweet trouble
It’s been sold out in recent years
300 must be done by tomorrow morning, otherwise it’s too late
Which one do you want this
The sound of the propeller is detected
One o'clock direction distance 5 miles depth 600
Are you those guys again?
No, this is the Schmidt class of the U.S. Navy
Behind is the Russian Alpha
I'm afraid that the nuclear-powered submarines of Britain and France are nearby
Are all countries listening to the truth?
Maintain strict air-to-submarine vigilance
Fighter jet takes off
Hawkeye calls Ibuki
The enemy fighter has taken off from the carrier
Five fighter jets are flying towards us
It's MiG. What's the distance now?
According to our fleet there are 400 miles
It’s about 20 minutes before reaching the enemy’s missile range.
Ibuki calls the ships
Prepare for air combat!
Prepare for air combat! Air combat...
-Prepare for air combat! -Prepare for air combat!
Enemy radar waves detected
We are locked
-What's the location?-Bearing 220, 75 miles away
Altitude 30,000 feet, speed Mach 1.8 remain unchanged
Five formations approach
Call me
Enemy plane launches missile
Eight of them came towards us, 50 miles away
-The enemy plane launches missiles.-Please, love eagle.
listen
All our training is for this moment
Yes
-Air combat preparation-Air combat preparation
Foredeck Vertical Launch System No. 1 to No. 8
Anti-air missile launch preparation
The gunner has 8 targets, don’t miss one
-Leave it to me-The target data has been entered
Ready to launch
emission!
Aiying launches air-to-air missiles, 8 missiles have entered the attack path
Contact with the target after 6 miles and 10 seconds
9 8 7 6
5 4 3 2
All missiles were destroyed
it is good
Destroy all missiles
All enemy missiles destroyed
-The gunner-in
The enemy plane is 5 formations, right?
5?
There are 8 enemy missiles
If each aircraft launches two, there will be one aircraft that has not attacked
The enemy plane was spotted at 11 o'clock
Has been spotted by Hawkeye’s radar
20 miles away, very low altitude approach!
Call Aiying Combat Information Center
This is love eagle
There was an aircraft invading at a very low altitude
It will spin up when attacking. Be sure to grasp that moment
Shoot it down
really
Bridge call combat information center
If the captain shoots it down at this distance,
Pilots may not escape
If you let him run
Next time he will launch missiles at us
Here is the battlefield
Contact Direction 200
5 miles away, height 100 feet
Air combat preparation
The enemy plane fired 2 missiles
Foredeck Vertical Missile System No. 9 to No. 11
Air missile launch preparation
Target data input completed
emission!
Love Eagle launches missiles
3 miles from target
Shoot down enemy missiles and fly towards enemy aircraft
Shot down
do not forget
This personal experience should be kept in mind
The deputy captain ordered the search for the pilot
Inform each ship
Don't give up, can't let him die
excuse me
How's it? Are you okay?
What was the explosion sound just now?
It's loud, isn't it serious
Only the sound is really scary
What's only sound
In addition, you two will take about 20 minutes
Please disembark
-Isn’t it two days as planned?-I’m getting off the boat
-Eh? -I want to disembark
-What good
Unsure of the survival of the pilot
Repeat Unable to determine the survival of the pilot
Our Self-Defense Force shot down an enemy plane for the first time
Took the life of the pilot
Now that the order for the defense has been given, this is a matter of course.
You said it
But there is no hesitation
Shinha Jisa
Have power
It is to be used without fear when necessary
We have destroyed two missiles launched by the enemy plane
Is it necessary to launch further attacks
The pilot will understand
Shot down?
The pilot was not rescued
is it
Cheer up
The highest commander of the Self-Defense Forces is you, Prime Minister
-This is different from what I said.-What
This doesn’t mean giving up the interview
Situation has changed
We have nothing. How are the injured people?
It's okay, please get on the helicopter and leave the ship early
Every time you say it's okay
It's okay, I said it's okay
Who said it’s okay? Don’t you want to send us back?
It’s dangerous on the deck. Go up.
-No, because-look
Miss Bendo Miss Bendo
Captain, let me ask you again
Does Japan need an aircraft carrier?
This is not a question I should answer
We must report what is happening here at this moment
Please let us stay on the boat
The next control will be stricter than before
-Why should I say that?-What
Japan's first aircraft carrier Ibuki
The secret operation in the Pacific Ocean is now fully revealed
Thank you
Yuzi will be fine, right?
She is not only in good health, but also has a strong heart
It's Christmas already
-Fujitang-Yes
If you think so, you lose
Sorry
Stopped the music
I came in to rest
-Oh, you worked hard. -You worked hard
I have a headache in what order to put the chocolate in
This Dutch one is delicious
But this Brazilian is also delicious
Ah this?
I plan to use this as Santa’s souvenir
Write a letter and put it in
Kids will be happy
You like everyone, everyone will like you too
Hush hush, don't make a noise
Why are you reading it out?
-What's this?-Let go
Put it in, put it in, put it all in
-Even if not today...-Why did you take it again
Emergency telegram received
Put down the antenna
Try to avoid battles that will affect future diplomatic negotiations
How to do
Self-defense force headquarters bulletin
Try to avoid battles that will affect future diplomatic negotiations
complete
Does it mean to avoid expanding from battle to war?
So what kind of scale is war?
Not only our self-defense officer is involved
When casualties spread to ordinary citizens
It's war
Try to avoid fighting
Propeller sound detected, bearing 190 degrees
Distance 8000 Depth 400
Is the submarine that attacked the Iphone
You're here again
The enemy ship opened the torpedo tube
-Open the launch tube? -It will definitely be launched this time
If you don’t kill it, Ibuki will be killed by it.
Captain, the enemy hasn't found us yet
The enemy ship has not changed its direction and is accelerating
Torpedo war preparation
Target enemy submarine
1 No. 2 tube launch preparation
The enemy launches an attack
Love Eagle Calls Ibuki
The enemy submarine fired 4 torpedoes at us
Deputy Captain Go to the bridge to operate the warship
(Bridge: It is located on the slightly higher deck in the middle of the warship, and is the command center in the ship)
Yes
Ibuki calls the ships
Fight submarine to avoid torpedoes
No one is allowed
Ready for submarine combat
-Facing torpedo, left full rudder -left full rudder
No. 3 and No. 4 launch inducer bomb
It's okay, okay, okay?
Mr. Tanaka is all right
Ah i'm fine
If the enemy torpedo is confused by the inducer,
Still get some time
Captain, if we don’t stop the next attack,
Iphone is dangerous
If you attack now, you can sink the enemy submarine.
If you attack, 150 enemy crew members will lose their lives.
but
Stop launch
Stop launching
-How far is it from the enemy submarine? -Distance 2000
OK, keep going straight
Maximum speed
Sonar reporting distance
700 650 600 550
The early tide approaches the enemy submarine
Route conflict
Distance 150
Are you planning to bump into it to stop the second wave of attacks?
If the operation is not good, a total of 300 people will sink to the sea floor
Torpedo giving up to induce a U-turn
Coming towards this ship
Ibuki Calls Hatsuki
Captain Seto
Leave it to me, I will solve it
emission
What is the depth difference between the early tide and the enemy submarine
Morning tide rises 5 meters
The enemy submarine began evasive action
Trim the bow while turning the rudder
Bow trim in the same direction
Will hit
Aslock anti-submarine missile hits enemy torpedo
A deviation is approaching Ibuki
Shot a torpedo
Start to evade
Zuo Man Ruo
Anti-shock preparation
Shock preparedness
Won't let you launch torpedoes anymore
The torpedo is coming
Zuo Man Ruo put on his helmet
Captain's order
Personnel from various positions on the port side quickly took refuge at the stern
Retreat quickly
fast!
Use my ship to protect Ibuki
Maximum speed meets torpedoes!
Maximum speed
Port side personnel have evacuated
You also go to the stern for refuge
Seto
The torpedo is coming, forward port side
you guys
I do not care what time
Can't leave his post
This is what the captain taught us
The torpedo is coming
Anti-shock preparation
Hello wait
There is nothing unusual in each department, right?
Launch tube chamber No abnormality
1L without exception
Command post flooded
No abnormalities in the AIP room
No abnormality in the machine room
What about the air pump
Air pump No abnormality
Good pressurized water tank drainage
Pressurized water tank drainage emergency float up
Emergency ascent
The morning tide and the enemy submarine came up together
Chuxue made our shield
Ibuki calls Shirayuki Isokaze
Ask the two ships to rescue the people on Chuxue
Head towards Haruma in two hours
Isokaze received
Roger that
Listen well, try to help Chuxue
Get ready for amphibious boat
Prepare amphibious boat
Where's the first snow
It's on fire, but Ibuki is fine
Please, Ibuki
The frigate's first snow is burning
Let's go back
The morning tide is heading towards Kure alone
The first snow can no longer sail, and many people were seriously injured.
Ibuki left Shirayuki to take care of the wounded
Head towards Hatsushima with Aihawk Isokaze
The participants of the UN Security Council have been assembled
Emergency meeting in three hours
is it
The self-defense officers at the battle scene have ordered the defense to be deployed
Still insist on special defense
(Dedicated defense: only use force around the domain to defend yourself when you are under attack)
Prime Minister, two ships have already been attacked
Now we should send reinforcements to defeat the opponent
Fujido
coming
From Yuko
-Eh what-what
Eh
Shaigu, news
-What is this-what, let me see
The frigate Hatsuki is burning
Nothing else
Yuzi, are you okay?
Hurry up and load emergency supplies on the helicopter
Repeat
Can i use this
Since I didn't get permission, I was also an accomplice
But this is the headline
When the report comes out, the society will be a mess
-Please.-Okay
-Thank you -Please come here next
Grandma Xiaolin bought so many things today
I told you it's going to fight
fight?
-Hurry up-ok
Not ok yet
Isn't it true? Is this true?
Prime Minister, the issue of Iki was posted on the Internet
what
Hey
How could it become like this
Deleted let them delete
Yes
Hold a press conference
No Prime Minister...
This video will definitely panic the public
Will there be a press conference later?
Now that it has happened
The top priority now is to gain the understanding and support of the people
If something goes wrong, the cabinet will be easily dissolved
Should we send reinforcements before the reception?
If you don’t use the force of the whole army to repel the enemy in one breath
We will really lose this war
Shiroyama
After World War II, a large number of politicians decided the direction of our country
Even though there are many discussions and complaints
They are united to stick to one thing
That is this country, Japan will never go to war
This is an agreement with the people
I hope you don’t use the word war lightly
Chief Cabinet Secretary is preparing to hold a press conference
(The Chief Cabinet Secretary of Japan is equivalent to the Secretary-General of the Government)
Yes
What a shocking video
I'm glad you showed our work status to the outside world
But I didn’t get permission to send the image, which violated the rules
I can only keep the satellite phone temporarily
By the way, wear your life jacket well
Ok
15 seriously injured
There was an explosion and fire near the bow of the ship
Chuxue shot near the bow
Multiple minor injuries (the number is still being confirmed)
A report from Chuxue
Many people were slightly injured 15 people were seriously injured
2 more people died
what
You say killed?
Who
Still confirming
Convey Captain Seto
Do a good job in the treatment of the crew and repair of the ship
Take the seriously injured who can move by helicopter to Okinotori Island
Captain Seto was seriously injured and now the deputy captain is in command
That's it, then pass it to the deputy captain
Yes
I buy this for my granddaughter at the nearby convenience store every year
She looks forward to this every year
Her name is Xiao Shang
I was going to wait for the interview to end
Just brought it back to her
I didn't expect these to be broken
Shall you eat it?
I'll buy it for my granddaughter
Everyone is good friend
The world is one home
That paragraph is well written
As long as you smile, everyone will be happy
Everyone is happy because of your smile
What's unhappy, let's face it together
Dreams will come true as long as there are dreams
There are two enemy ships ahead. They are destroyers.
Bearing 190 and 45 miles away
Driving to Hatsushima
This is determined to intercept us
If it’s the Northern Fleet of the East Asian Federation, it’s Russa and Sligo.
Both ships are equipped with YJ95 anti-ship missiles
These two ships must be rendered ineffective
-Short-range defense weapon system Check fuel-Understand
I think Isokaze should take the lead
It’s safer to sink them with the Harpoon anti-ship missile.
If you use a harpoon, the ship will sink
The two ships together have 600 crew members
Do you want to take the lives of all of them
In this case, there is no doubt that the enemy will use this as an opportunity to expand the front
It would also violate the command of the command "avoid fighting that affects diplomatic negotiations"
I blame the reporter for leaking the news and inciting people’s anxiety
Since it is the Northern Fleet of East Asia
That should also be equipped
Long-range missiles that can snipe Japan from the sea
Judging from the situation so far, they cannot be judged by common sense
International law makes no sense to them
If you stimulate them again
In case you hurt the nation
Then it will trigger the war you call
Our Self-Defense Force exists to avoid war
Our judgment will be the fuse of the war
As a self-defense player
Do not
As a crew member
I can't agree
The enemy ship is coming
How about Isokaze’s main gun, Deputy Captain?
So it won’t sink the enemy ship
Main gun
Try it
Main gun?
Be sure to show me when you were a gunner in Pufeng
The ability to take first place many times in military competition
Don't have to wear a high hat for me
I'll do what you want me to do
understand
Enemy destroyer
Speed ​​25 nautical miles 35 miles away
The ship’s main gun has a range of 20 miles
5 miles longer than the opponent’s main gun
Make good use of this gap
Indeed, if the main gun is used
Can minimize the damage to enemy ships
But the range is only 20 miles, we will also enter the opponent’s radar circle
It is very dangerous
Didn't the headquarters order the defense to be deployed?
Why worry about the enemy...
Isn’t your usual training just for today...
Don't you want to show it
But the enemy will definitely launch anti-ship missiles
Ah will come
Captain, can I use extended range bombs for shelling?
Extended projectile range to 60 miles
-No-what
The damage to the hit point will be great if the bomb is extended
Must be close to 20 miles or so to strike
-Here, Kansai-style.-What?
This is a sign of your seriousness
Oh, really
I confiscated the satellite phone of the female reporter
Isokaze, the enemy ship is 10 miles away.
I've warned her seriously, I'm leaving now
-Inoue 3 Zuo-In
The ship is 40 miles away from the enemy destroyer
Repeat, this ship is 40 miles away from the enemy destroyer
Yes
Now our country is being invaded by the East Asian Federation
Whether it’s shooting down enemy fighters or fighting with the 5th escort
All out of self-defense, in accordance with the constitution
Did the Prime Minister have to hold a press conference because of Yuko's video?
Breaking news: East Asian Federation forces occupy Hatsushima?
The Self-Defense Forces began their first defense deployment
The current constitution explains the right to self-defense like this
To protect the personal freedom, safety and property of our citizens
Allow the use of the minimum necessary force
Ah, that's mine
give me one
Except Mentaiko
Can't it? Mentaiko
Can't
Would you like to try my dried cheese katsuobushi?
Not needed
Prime Minister, this is Imai from Hyundai Daily
The fighters that shot down the East Asian Federation were clearly at war
Isn't it the use of force?
No
As i just said
This is based on the right to self-defense
Instead of exercising the right to war
Oh my mentha
please wait for a moment
Sorry
Hello, hurry up
Instant noodles and water are out of stock
The phone at the headquarters’ distribution center couldn’t be reached at all
I can't go back after seeing this for a while, obviously I'm off work
Just about the use of force
The aircraft carrier Ibuki caused heated discussions!
The personnel concerned have fled abroad! ? Japan is chaotic.
Does Japan have an aircraft carrier
Only the minimum necessary force is allowed
Is there going to be a war?
Japan is over
Terrorism is about to spread to Japan! ?
Is this fake news? (laughs)
Is the third world war going to start! ?
Our government strictly abides by this regulation
what! What about the concert that weekend?
What a shame! ! I will hate you if it is cancelled! !
Will the United States help us?
There is nothing in the nearby convenience store
If this is true, it would be terrible. What should I do?
Ibuki is on fire, the news is endless
The East Asian Federation illegally arrested a maritime security officer
The aircraft carrier will be suspended if it burns
Has the government issued any statement?
Haole, ready to escape
Please the Self-Defense Forces! Hold Japan for me! !
This is a super awesome video
I've thought that there will be such a day
Occupy our territory
Who are you at war with?
My cat is also very upset
What on earth is Prime Minister Tarimizu thinking?
On this basis, attack the frigate of the Self-Defense Force
An anti-war demonstration will be held in the National Diet Building at 12 tomorrow
Please participate! Together to protect peaceful Japan!
Yeah, go abroad
I want to know the details
The war is too horrible, is it really being attacked by missiles?
what! ! The war is really going to start! ?
What did Japan learn from the Pacific War? Is the Japanese government a fool?
Is there any renewal?
Not only caused several injuries, but unfortunately several more people died
Ibuki is so handsome, although it is on fire
Until now, this is a battle that has to be fought for self-defense
I am Ichinose of Toho Shimbun
All the responses so far have been out of self-defense
As a last resort
But after that, the war will escalate and intensify
If there are 100 East Asian Federation fighters attacking us
Then we must shoot down these 100 fighters
In turn, it will cost 100 pilots.
Isn’t this just what the world calls war?
No this is not war
This is just a battle for self-defense from beginning to end
It’s just that in order to prevent further development
Tried everything
Won't cause war again
After the wars of the past, we and the Constitution swear together
Don't provide people with inaccurate information to cause their misunderstanding
Please trust our government
Our country will never participate in war
Prime Minister, have you ever negotiated with the East Asian Federation
Has the East Asian Federation issued a statement
Prime Minister, can we think
It was the service of Ishu that triggered this incident
Prime Minister please answer
Prime minister prime minister
Prime Minister!
The enemy's anti-ship missile is approaching
Anti-aircraft missile ready to launch
-Hit-launch
The short-range SAM missile shot down two enemy missiles
One broke through the line of defense
It’s 10 miles away and arrives at this ship in 20 seconds.
Short-range defense weapon system
Confirm to shoot down all missiles
Isn't this preventable
How is the enemy dynamic
The direction and speed have not changed. The two ships are approaching.
20 miles from the ship
Is about to enter the range of the main gun
Holler, sure shelling ray
Go around on the right side of Rusa
Full right rudder
-Maximum battle speed -Maximum battle speed
Please, Isokaze
Already at 90 degrees of the target destroyer
Ray has been determined
Gunner
I have to hit the target every time
The next step is to race against time
Don't give them time to fight back
Understand full calibration shooting control manual
The first goal: enemy destroyer Rusa
Missile launch tube aiming completed
-Hit-launch
First target confirm hit
Second target fore deck
Anti-aircraft missile launch tube aiming completed
hit
emission
Captain Sligo is approaching
10 o'clock direction 16 miles away
Greet Russa first
Second target confirm hit
The third target, rear deck, torpedo tube, aiming completed
Keep calling me
emission
Confirm to hit all targets on Rusa
Sligo is approaching Isokaze
10 o'clock direction 15 miles away
Will call at 12 miles
Sligo approaches, keeps the same direction, 14 miles away
The artillery commander will then hit the main gun on the front deck
Do you shoot again?
There is no time to confirm the ray, hurry up
Is the target fore deck main gun
Detected enemy ship radar waves, we are locked
Aiming
hit
emission
Isokaze, shelling is coming
Stop on both sides
Rewind at full speed, fast, reverse
Stop on both sides, reverse at full speed, fast
Flash away
Escaped
Missed
Both enemy ships have lost their combat effectiveness
Isokaze unscathed
Great
Worthy of being the captain of the floating ship
I'll report to the commander
The information center calls the bridge, the obstacles have been cleared in the field of vision
Repeat Obstacles have been cleared in the field of view
captain
Whether we or the enemy
Tried their best not to cause casualties
Everyone has the same idea, right
If you sink those two warships
From an international humanitarian perspective, we must help the survivors
Especially the deputy captain, aren’t you very tough on this?
For our fleet, the top priority is to reach the sea area of ​​Boriu.
Don't have the time and energy to do that
That's it, Mr. Xinbo
I really miss it
Among the 54th National Defense Graduates
Only you, Qiujin Ryota, will add "Mr." to the name of your classmate
I haven't changed since then
We are capable of war
But never go to war
I still remember it in my heart and stand here
Some things cannot be guarded without fighting
The difference between you and me seems to have not changed
Not only one thing is the same
Is your family going to have a second child?
what
Let your children embrace the dream of the future and live a peaceful life
Japan must become such a country
To protect Japan, everyone has the same belief
I didn't expect that you would say this when you are single
I used to think that you were out of gregariousness from the beginning of the national defense era
More suitable for the Air Self-Defense Force
Been here for half a year
I still don’t understand why Mr. Xinbo chose the Maritime Self-Defense Force
Boarding the boat is equivalent to handing over each other's lives
Whether in battle or death
It’s not easy to understand that all alone in the fighter.
Next, the situation will be more severe
An hour ago, the UN Security Council started
We explained what happened to all countries as much as possible
But they have their own plans
I'm afraid it will take time to draw a conclusion
If possible, they don’t want to get involved with this, right?
-Then I will leave first.-Yeah
The constitution prohibits participation in war and military preparation
But to ensure independence, every country has the right to self-defense
This is a natural right above the constitution
To resist foreign invasion
Must have a minimum of armed
The right to self-defense has become a reality
The Self-Defense Forces carry the history after World War II
Is fighting hard now
We must not make leadership mistakes
The European branch and the French Minister of Foreign Affairs Apollo have made an appointment
45 minutes later, there is a telephone conversation with the Minister of Foreign Affairs Seongsan
Is negotiating with other permanent members through the diplomatic channel
Ethiopian Presidency
Non-permanent members Ukraine Uruguay Italy
And G7 chair country Canada
Tell this to the UN delegation
In today's era
Everyone knows that wars between nations will inevitably create risks that affect the global economy
If you make good use of this, the UN’s response may also change.
Yes
Submarines from various countries have surfaced again
They are still behind us and there is one more ship
Is a Chinese submarine
Are all the major countries of the United Nations gathered?
Hawkeye calls Ibuki
This is Ibuki
MiG-35 takes off from an enemy aircraft carrier
A total of ten flew to Ibuki
Altitude 30,000 feet, speed 1.5 Mach
30 minutes to arrive
Captain, if ten planes are not deployed, it is difficult to ensure safety
Listen, the enemy has increased its attack
Albatross Captain
It's time for us to attack
Needless to say, what is needed most now is teamwork
Trust and be trusted by wingmen, team members and renovators
Support each other and firmly believe that they are the main force of the Air Self-Defense Force and show pride
Albatross
Then you have to calmly deal with whatever situation you encounter
Let them see the results of our training
understand
Information Center This is the carrier-based aircraft warehouse. The elevator has been repaired.
Captain, have you caught up?
Well done
The 92nd Flight Group is ready to attack
Repeat the 92nd flight group, ready to attack
Commander Yuanshang: This is battle, not training
If it is entangled by an enemy plane, it is allowed to shoot down
Yes, instructions to the pilot
The first is to warn that the enemy will not move, I will not move
Plus
Yes
If you are confused...
Fire if you are confused
This is what the captain said
If you are confused, fire
Amulet that bless me not lost
Albatross 2 ready to go
understand
Five have taken off
excuse me
This is a sympathy meal prepared by the captain for the two of you
Please eat while hot
Thank you
The condolences prepared by the captain himself
-Ah-Satellite phone
5 to 10
Fire if you are confused
But i'm lost
Hawkeye Calls the Albatross
Five aircraft of the MiG-35 front team launched missiles
10 rounds in total, 50 miles away
Attention team, this is Albatross 1
Allow weapons to fire at will
Let's fight each other with the target
Release inducer
The Albatross were not shot
Information Center Calling Albatross 1
Keep the missile's range to avoid a two-to-one situation
Understand, attention, team, this is Albatross 1.
Don’t target all 10
Take the rising enemy aircraft formation as the Alpha team and the forward formation as the Beta team
Go around Alpha's left wing
Don't care about beta
Target 5 of Alpha Team
Each decides that the prey is ready to attack
Distance 25 This time it's my turn
Tooth for tooth launch
OK, shoot down two
10 o'clock direction enemy missile
Dodge all enemy missiles
(Deception paper: a small piece of metal shot to confuse the enemy's radar tracking and locking)
Now everyone's deception paper and inducement bullets are finished
Confirm to shoot down the fourth Alpha
None of the Albatross planes were shot
Was not shot by such an attack
6 enemy planes left
Returning pilots usually leave a missile for pursuit
In other words, they have 6 missiles left
Air combat requires a lot of fuel
Considering the return distance, maybe another 2 or 3 minutes is the limit.
Then, the albatross team won, right?
Let's talk through this time
Locked
Hawkeye Calls the Albatross
Enemy plane launches missile
6 enemy aircraft launched at the same time to take evasive action
Albatross number 2 calls number 1
6 enemy missiles, all targets are local
6 pieces all
Albatross 2 Turn right and maneuver to escape towards the sea
Roger that
Kakinuma, hold on
Pull up when there is still 6000 from the sea
not good
Kakinuma fast ejection
Reduce speed and leave the cabin
Captain this fighter
15 billion
idiot
Fighter can replace
You can't replace
Kakinuma catapult
Kakinuma
I am irreplaceable
The enemy plane retreated
Check if 1st Lieutenant Kakinuma survived
At the same time, confirm whether the enemy pilot is alive
Yes
Where's the pilot
Is searching now
I haven't found his trace yet
The helicopter caught the distress signal
Confirming whether it has opened the lifeboat
Catapult at that speed is very dangerous
Believe he is still alive
captain
Even if you order a fighter plane,
The enemy aircraft carrier has 60 fighters
We only have 15 which is a quarter of theirs
Even if you shoot down 4 enemy fighters,
It’s also very unfortunate that we lost 1 fighter
The enemy also judged this way
The battle will be more severe
Be mentally prepared
Yes
Don’t be proud even if you shoot down 4 enemy aircraft
Does he mean this
No, he wanted to thank you
thank
Just let Lieutenant Kakinuma eject and escape
What he said can’t be less
Means not wanting to lose anyone
Found 1st Captain Kakinuma and confirmed his survivor
Deputy Captain Order
Each department takes turns dining
Everyone, are you hungry?
Eat first
Yes
Anti-air and anti-submarine security continues to be tight
Prime Minister good news
The helicopter rescued Lieutenant Kakinuma from the cabin
An enemy pilot was found on the way back
And rescued it
Just caught a prisoner
Saved two lives
good news
No enemy target is found in the field of view
Repeat again, no enemy target is found in the field of vision
The departments are taking turns dining
Morale is high
is it
How is the status of the enemy pilot
No trauma found
But still not regaining consciousness
Roger that
Send to the infirmary after returning
I hope we can rescue the East Asian Federation pilot
Be able to communicate to each other smoothly
smoothly
In order to achieve mutual understanding
I can go
Don't move please lie down
Hello hello
doing what
Quick to subdue him
stop
Stop, stop
What are you holding
It's dangerous to go out
Can not be done
Kakinuma
You bastard
Look at what you did
Don't shoot
Captain, this guy killed Lieutenant Kakinuma.
He has no weapons anymore
We rescued him and he came back alive
But
It must be cold in the sea
Tonight is christmas eve
I don’t know the tradition of your country
In Japan
We will celebrate this holiday but it has nothing to do with faith
We just want to be able to peacefully
Spend this day
Take him to the detention room
Give him another hot drink
Yes
-Come.-It's okay. Let's go
Lieutenant Kakinuma will leave it to you
Yes
Return to their posts
Don't shoot
The world is one home
Everyone is good friend
cheer up
I saw a blazing flame on the frigate today
I saw someone falling down covered in blood
Where's the Minister of Foreign Affairs
Is having a phone conversation with the Chinese ambassador
In 5 hours, we have had telephone conversations with diplomats from eight countries
Still motivated
Don't look at him like that
The heart for the country is much stronger than others
The chairman of the Security Council just now
Called the UN Ambassador Nomura
Calling
Hawkeye calls Ibuki
The enemy fighter takes off from the aircraft carrier
Strengthen air vigilance
The vanguard has 4
A total of 24 aircraft with the main force
Now even the anti-ship missiles are coming
I will confirm that the ship is sealed and prepare to deal with the attack of enemy aircraft
The Albatross fighter plane is under preparation
The first to take off is a total of 10 fighters from the Sparrows and the White Doves
The sparrows and the white doves are ready to attack
I’m Bendo. I’m reporting from the aircraft carrier Ibuki.
Are you ok?
it should be no problem
Ok send to the world
Your English is good
No no no
send
Zone 3 Zone 4 closed
Sparrow team white pigeon team
Take off immediately when you're ready
Roger that
Please let me go
I understand the characteristics of enemy aircraft
can
But don't think about revenge
Will make you lose your judgment
There are torpedoes at 2 o'clock
15 miles away, total of 8
The departure of the morning tide is very bad for us
Information center call bridge
Deputy Captain, you will direct the anti-submarine battle
Received right full rudder
Right full rudder
Decoy No. 1 No. 2 No. 3 No. 4 Ready to launch
Ready to launch bait
Ibuki Calls Love Eagle
I'll leave the torpedo to you
Roger that
Ready to launch Aslock anti-submarine missile
Aslock launches an attack
Ready to launch
emission
Prime Minister, the United Nations called
I am Tarumi
Destroy 6
2 more are missiles
Keep approaching
Proximity Defense System
All enemy missiles were destroyed
-4 enemy fighters fired missiles again-8 in total
8 missiles are approaching
(SM2: Standard 2 air defense missile)
Launch SM2 missiles
SM2 missiles 11 to 18 are ready to launch
hit
emission
8 enemy missiles have been destroyed
This is the greeting from the 4 fighters of the vanguard
After meeting with the main force, they will rush over in one breath
The artillery commander, take good care
Roger that
Strict air security
Repeat it again
24 fighters are here
Maximum speed of each ship
Sailing in a zigzag
Maximum speed
Zigzag sailing
I am Yuan Shang
Under missile attack
As a result, fighters from behind the 2nd plane cannot take off
Only 1 fighter
Can you hear it?
Yes
One fighter plane alone cannot fight 24 enemy planes
Can it fly close to the sea and approach an enemy aircraft carrier?
Roger that
The enemy formation is less than 75 miles away
Attack target 1st to 24th enemy aircraft formation
Attack at 50 miles
SM2 missiles 21 to 44 are ready to launch
What is the current height of the water
50 feet above the sea
Listen, penetrate the splint of the enemy aircraft carrier
Don’t let their subsequent fighters take off
Roger that
Press water
Yes
Be careful not to spin up
Roger that
Thank you
Will the store manager come out?
I went to see
Hurry up
very sorry
Sorry please wait
What's up? Really, I've been waiting for a long time
The enemy formation entered within 50 miles of our side
Has entered the range of the anti-ship missile
Air combat
Can't let go of an enemy plane
Target enemy fighter
Start attack
emission
Our target is the enemy aircraft and missiles that Aiying missed
Give me all in one pot
Yes
Air combat, ready to launch SM2 missiles
Data input is complete, launch preparation is complete
hit
emission
Captain is a submarine
And 5 ships
Bearing 190 and 12 miles away
Between the enemy carrier and us
Have been lurking there
Aihawk Isokaze
Anti-submarine combat preparation
The submarine launched a torpedo
10 pieces in total
Anti-submarine warfare begins, ready to launch decoys
The torpedo’s offensive route is scattered
5 shots towards us
The remaining 5 rounds
Towards the enemy fleet
Heading to enemy aircraft carrier
what
Can you hear the pressure?
Yes
Stop attack
what
Leave the battlefield immediately
Roger that
The torpedo is coming
captain
Blew up?
There is also the sound of torpedo explosions around the enemy fleet
Hit?
No, I blew myself up close like us
5 submarines floated
what is the problem
Signal recognition
Is the UN Force
The entire fleet bears the logo of the United Nations force
Does the United Nations allow the fighting to continue to escalate?
The enemy plane dispersed
Caught up
The enemy carrier fleet changed its course
it is good
Is this also what you expected
Overcoming difficulties
Not just us
I know
Hatsushima’s fishing fleet has all left the island
is it
Five permanent members participate in the UN forces at the same time
End local disputes
For the first time ever
indeed
In the future, our job is
How to make the other person understand their mistakes
Not true diplomacy
Is to pursue the practical happiness of both countries
And never achieve justice
Never take this step, not drive the opponent into desperation
It's also our diplomatic posture, right?
Yes, take it seriously
-understand
But the development of things
Always unexpected
Don't shoot
captain
This guy killed Lieutenant Kakinuma
He has no weapons anymore
We rescued him and he came back alive
But but
Can't shoot
I saw a blazing flame on the frigate today
I saw someone falling down covered in blood
My legs trembled and I couldn't move
This is war
This must never happen
Never allowed
I naturally have such thoughts in my heart
But there are also battles to prevent war
Although very contradictory
But this is also true
Whether battle will develop into war
Is the responsibility of all of us in this world
Even if it will be sad
remorse
Someone will sacrifice
I have to keep working hard until the day when there is no dispute in the world
The world is gradually becoming a whole...
The above is the report sent by Yuko Honda from the aircraft carrier Ibuki
I’m Bendo. I’m reporting from the aircraft carrier Ibuki.
Good morning
The crisis of war has dissipated
Full-scale conflict has been avoided
The team that occupied Hatsushima has also left
Now the 5th escort group centered on the aircraft carrier Ibuki
Is continuing to maintain the silver guard against air and submarine
Not silver, strict, strict
Continue to maintain strict alert against air and submarine
Going to Hatsushima to rescue the maritime security officer
Pain pain
what
Sorry sorry
I accidentally fell asleep
But I have done it well
I will cheer for 20%
20%, let me go
Eh
what happened
Xiaojing Xiaojing
Xiaojing, is this the thief?
Xiaojing, are you hurt?
give me
What water?
Christmas gift
Christmas
this one
If you don't dislike this, then
Give you
Merry Christmas
what
Merry christmas santa
Merry Christmas
What happened
Hotan, you scared me to death. What are you doing?
Go for a drink
Is there still a shop open after this order?
Don't underestimate Tokyo
Everything here
Also
But I won't go
why
My kid should get up
How old is your child
5 years old exactly 5 years old
To you merry christmas
For 5 year olds
You have been with the company since yesterday, haven't you
So no matter what I am the boss
How to say
Mean
But the meaning in this case is its original meaning
No matter what
Merry Christmas all over Japan
Did not cause a situation where both sides were hurt
The conclusion is that there is a tie
But as a result of diplomatic negotiations
This is also the most ideal
If 100 vs. 0 wins
The hatred of the loser will never disappear
It’s the result of a big country pushing a small country to a dead end
That made the world today
The side dishes of the bento are always egg rolls and octopus sausage
After complaining to my mother, I was beaten by my father for the first time
The wife asked the younger son several times what to wear for the entrance ceremony
For grandson’s birthday, grandparents started busy early in the morning
I struggled with what Christmas gifts to buy for my lover for 10 days
Buying a house is a lifetime thing
Then one day, I sent my parents away with gratitude
I say Shidu
We want to protect
Just these ordinary happiness
Humble and tiny happiness
For this we will become politicians
Yes
OK, let's hold a press conference
it is good
Shidu
Can i work for another 3 years
In-ship patrol 2nd equipped 2nd straight sentry
Deputy captain
Yes
Order the cooking class, prepare hot rice balls and miso soup
it is good
Waiting for our brothers at Hatsushima
Should be hungry
Give them food first
I thought pilots wouldn’t care if others were hungry
You don't know enough
I'll get them to prepare
Vice Captain, my meal
Send it to the captain's room as usual
Do not
I want to eat with everyone in the cafeteria
Do you want to talk about the anecdote of your own fighter?
I want to hear everyone tell the story of this ship and the sea
understand
Summarize and organize the sentry equipment on the ship
It's the second direct sailing duty, please be prepared
Hot
This is hot
Masato Kakinuma